sabpaisa.in 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy holds an utmost importance to us. We recognize the need to protect the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number) you share with us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We endeavour to comply with laws of other countries but cannot and do not warrant that we do. We would like to assure you that we follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our websites. The Privacy Policy is applicable to the websites of SRS Live Technologies Pvt. Ltd. SRS Live Technologies Pvt. Ltd. (SRS) consists of [http://sabpaisa.in](http://sabpaisa.in/), SabPaisa Mobile Application, and SRS Live Technologies Pvt. Ltd. This privacy statement also does not apply to the websites of our business partners, corporate affiliates or to any other third parties, even if their websites are linked to our Websites. We recommend you review the privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact. 

For the purposes of this privacy policy,   
**"Corporate affiliates"** means any entity or joint venture that is wholly or partially owned or controlled by SRS Live Technologies Pvt. Ltd.   
**"Business partners"** means any subcontractor, vendor or other entity with whom we have an ongoing business relationship to provide products, services, or information.   
Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.   
The following terms governs the collection, use and protection of your Personal Information by the Website. This Privacy Policy shall be applicable to users or customers who purchases any services from the Website or visits the Website. By visiting and/ or using the Website you have agreed to our Privacy Policy.   
**We categorise information about you (collectively referred to as "Personal Information") as follows:**   

  1. **Profiling:** Information which you provide when you register for a Service, which may include some or all of the following:- Information about your personal identity such as gender, marital status, age, preferences, likes and dislikes etc; and your contact details such as your physical addresses, postal addresses, telephone and fax numbers and the like. - In the case of Facebook aligned services (if so opted by you), publicly available information of your friends, their likes and dislikes, etc.
  2. **Payment and Account:** Your account history with us including (without limitation) all billing information and communications, payment history etc. We maintain this in encrypted form on secure servers.
  3. **Service Usage:** Information about your navigation using our Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads.
  4. **Log information:** Information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request.
  5. **Transactional Information:** Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities.
  6. **Correspondence Information:** Content, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our Services, which include email communications, blog, chat room and discussion board communications, instant message communications, experts forum communications, faxmail communications, membership of mailing lists etc.
  7. **User IDs:** Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services.
  8. **Stored Information:** Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc.

**We only collect your Personal Information to conduct our business and to enable us to deliver and improve our Services. We do not for any reason whatsoever sell your Personal Information to any third party or otherwise trade on it.** We will only disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If we want to use it for any other purpose, we will obtain your prior written consent. If you decline to submit personal information to us, then we will unfortunately not be in a position to provide the Services to you. Any of your information which you provide when you use certain Services and are to an open, public environment or forum including (without limitation) any blog, community or discussion board, is not confidential, does not constitute Personal Information, and is not subject to protection under Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy explains the following: 

What Information we collect from you and why?  
With whom (if anyone) your Information is shared?  
You can opt - out of receiving our promotional e - mails?  
Security measures we take to protect your Information?  
Other information you should know about your privacy?  

When browsing our Website, you are not required to provide any Personal Information unless and until you choose to make a purchase or sign up for one of our e-mail newsletters or other services as described below.

**Purchase our Services**  
In order to purchase services through our Website, we ask for certain Personal Information/s such as your name, credit card number and expiration date, credit card billing address, telephone number, e - mail address and the name or names of the person(s), who would be using such services. We require this information to process, fulfill and confirm your transactions and keep you informed of each transaction's status. 

**User Registration** If you choose to become a registered user of Website, we look for your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, a unique login name, password, and password validation, and a password hint to help you remember your password. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including but not limited to:

  1. Personal identification
  2. To allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary
  3. To customize the content of our site to strive to meet your specific needs; and/or
  4. To make product or other improvements to our site.
  5. As a Registered user you will also occasionally receive updates from us about seminars, workshops, fairs, and other noteworthy items. However, you may choose at any time to no longer receive these types of e - mail messages. Please see our Opt - Out Policy described below for details.

**Online Surveys**  
We value opinions and comments from users, so we frequently conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated, and used to make improvements to the Website and its services and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for Website users. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.

**Automatic Logging of Session Data**  
We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any Personal Information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on the Website. An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the Website the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyze such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the Website, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the Website, how long visitors to the Website are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.

**Cookies** From time to time, we may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies certain features of the site may not function property or at all as a result.

**Other**  
From time to time we may add or enhance services available on the Website. To the extent these services are provided, and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making the Website the better and easier to use. 

If we are required to intercept, disclose, monitor and/or store your Personal Information:

  1. by law;
  2. to conduct our business;
  3. to secure our systems; or
  4. to enforce our own rights, we will do so in the manner as prescribed by law.

If you would want not to receive our newsletters, promotional campaigns, valuable information related but not limited to your area of interest, and any other information from our business associates, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in each e - mail message or send us an email at [unsubscribe@srslive.in](mailto:unsubscribe@srslive.in) SRS reserves the right to limit users to those who will accept e - mails. Users will be notified via e - mail prior to any actions taken. 

We safeguard your privacy using known security standards and procedures and comply with applicable privacy laws. Our websites combine industry-approved physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure that your information is well protected though it's life cycle in our infrastructure.

Sensitive data is hashed or encrypted when it is stored in our infrastructure. Sensitive data is decrypted, processed and immediately re-encrypted or discarded when no longer necessary. We host web services in audited data centers, with restricted access to the data processing servers. Controlled access, recorded and live-monitored video feeds, 24/7 staffed security and biometrics provided in such data centers ensure that we provide secure hosting. 

Website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which SRS Group has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords, and your Website membership account information.
